Let's open the CLOAD interface, and we first enter the module drawing.
In the module drawing, we have newly added a folding shirt module.
In the past, the folding shirt would use a fixed front and a folded back.
This is more time-consuming.
Now we have added two types.
One is circular, and the other is triangular.
We use the circular as an example.
You can see that there are five shapes here.
And there are two types of front clothes.
The main difference between the front clothes and the back clothes is the fold.
The main difference between the sleeves is the number of folds.
And there are two types of sleeves.
One is circular, the other is rectangular.
And there is a collar.
First, let's load the collar.
Then, let's load the front clothes.
Next, let's load the back clothes.
The loading process is a bit slow.
And, let's add a sleeve.
And, let's add a sleeve cuff.
Finally, let's add the pocket.
As for the tie, you can add what you need.
If you don't need it, you don't need to add it.
Now you can see that this shirt is folded.
Next, let's go to the physical window to see the fabric.
We can see that this fabric has no texture.
If you need texture, you can add the texture according to your needs.
Let's click on the details of the fabric.
The difference between the details and the previous one is that
it increases the bending strength and the deformation force on the corner line.
This is mainly an optimization of the fabric.
As you know, in the previous version,
Printed Out can only be done when the clothes have texture.
Now, although this shirt has no texture,
it can still be Printed Out.
We can see here that
we can change the different fabrics to see the simple material situation.
As I just mentioned,
our fabric has increased the bending strength of the corner line
and the deformation force of the corner line.
Let's open the fabric calculation mode.
As you can see, in the previous version,
we had to enter the data we measured according to the next step.
Now, we can enter all the data.
We can jump to this interface.
We can input the measured data into this interface at a time.
This is an optimization of the fabric calculation mode.
Now, let's go back to the simulation mode.
Let's take a look at the library window.
We can see that in the previous version,
in addition to Fibrous, there is a blue download button.
In Hardware and Trace, there is also a blue download button.
Now, in addition to these two,
there is also a blue download button on Apert and Fibrous.
In the previous version,
we had to click on the Fibrous download button to do one-click download.
Now, we can download one by one according to our own needs.
For example, we click here to Apert.
We can see that there is a single download button in Apert.
We can click here to download.
This download takes a little time.
Let's wait a little bit.
Now, the download is finished.
In other libraries, it is the same.
Each with a blue button has a new download content.
You can download it according to your needs.
In the model section,
the male and female models each added two.
Among them, the female model added Feifei and Grace.
Among them, the male model added Henry and Nate.
The male model added Henry and Nate.
In this model,
the female model added Andy and the male model added Henry.
The male model added Andy and the female model added Danny.
Now, open Feifei.
Open Feifei.
After opening Feifei,
we can see that there is a size folder in this.
This is different from the previous model.
In this size folder,
There are some data from the American Experimental Materials Association.
There are three main categories.
The first one is Miffy.
She is a female with a more delicate figure.
Potatoe is a female with a slightly shorter figure.
Whereas Glass is a female with a fatter figure.
The difference between Curvy and Stripe is that Curvy is more beautiful than Stripe.
In the class, we can see that the model is getting fatter by applying a single size.
The male model is also the same.
In the male model, there is an app called Modular Configurator.
It mainly covers the main models when modeling.
Because every time the version is updated, the model size will change.
It will affect the use of modeling.
So from 5.1,
we started to provide special models for the Modular Configurator.
These models can't change the size.
They can only use hair, shoes, posture, and movements.
Let's take a look at the first model.
You can see that the motion is back to the stage.
But this motion is only for Emma and Kelly.
In the male model, it's the same.
It's only for Daryl and Martin.
The male model has made a big change.
So when we were developing,
we only had two models for the Modular Configurator.
You may know that in the previous model,
there was no gender for the model.
But now,
there is no gender for the model that is over 7 years old.
There is no gender for the model that is below 7 years old.
Because our data library is for 8 to 16 years old,
when we were doing the Modular Configurator,
we recommended that everyone be 8 to 12 years old.
It's the most accurate.
Why is there a number here that is 7 to 20 years old?
This is mainly because we did an age extension on the basis of 8 to 16 years old.
But it's just a reference.
If your age is an unrecognized model,
but your body shape is an adult model,
then we still recommend that everyone use an adult model to convert.
Next, let's do an edit on the model in the computer editor.
Let's change its height a little higher.
You can see that when you change the height,
there is a height size mark in 3D.
It's the same when you change the height.
After that, we will make a change to the model.
In the past, when we changed the posture,
we couldn't do the absolute symmetry.
We all look at it with the naked eye.
Now, there is a small icon on the top of the locator.
Let's click on it.
Then we can do the symmetrical posture edit.
This is when we edit the model posture.
Next, let's take a look at some changes in the first one.
In the previous version, the first one is not divided into adult model and child model.
In the current version, it is divided into adult model and child model.
Adult model and child model are two different models.
In the fabric, we can see that
there are some hair fabrics added.
There are six types of hair fabrics added.
Including Anglaise wool, fox wool, water-coloured leather, fur-coloured wool, etc.
In addition, we can see some wool-coated fabrics.
The difference between the wool-coated fabrics here is that
they are different in weight.
We can see some changes in the right-hand view of the logo.
At the same time, we can see that some hair fabrics are added separately.
At this time, when you select the fabric in the preview,
if you don't want to use the automatically generated hair fabrics,
you can use the normal map to find the hair fabrics.
In the headwear and trims,
you can see that the washing texture has been moved to the headwear and trims.
In addition, in this ribbon, which is the fox's head,
there is an additional part.
In addition, in this ribbon, which is the fox's head, there is an additional part.
In the walkthrough process, we often need some stages to match.
As you can see, there are four different stage objects in this stage.
You can choose from them.
Next, we will introduce in detail what new features have been updated by making a new outfit.
First, we add a model.
Then we import the DXF file.
Now, we import the DXF file.
There is no decoding on the side of the model.
We can use the tool to compare the length of the panel.
We compare the distance between the two panels from the sleeve to the waistline.
When we reach the waistline, we can click the right button.
There are three types of options.
The first is the length of the panel.
The length of the panel means that the decoding is added on the back of the rolling panel.
The fixed panel is on the unmoved panel.
The fixed panel is on the front panel.
The two panels are on both panels.
We select two panels here.
After selecting, we click the return button to complete.
Now you can see that both the front panel and the back panel have been added to the decoding.
Now the panel is only half.
We want to match the other half.
Naturally, we can think of the symmetrical panel and the sewing line.
There is a new function similar to the symmetrical panel and the sewing line.
It is called symmetrical.
Open the sewing line.
We click the right button on the panel.
We can see that the panel has been opened.
And it also has a symmetrical effect.
Let's change the position of the sewing line.
We can see that the two sides are changed at the same time.
We can use the panel line expansion tool to change the length of the panel.
But we can only make it longer.
Now, in addition to making it longer, we can also shrink it inward.
For example, we shrink it in here by one centimeter.
And we can make it one centimeter longer.
We can make it one centimeter longer by one centimeter.
And we can make it one centimeter longer by one centimeter.
After changing the panel, we usually want to measure the size of the corresponding parts.
For example, how much is the chest and how much is the waist.
Here we can use the measurement tool.
It's not the same as before.
We can use the drawing tool to complete it.
We click the start button to end the double-click.
We can see the size.
Here we can see its size.
Let's take a look.
We enter its name from the windowiance box on the right side.
Although there is an empty space in the center,
The length of the panel is not dense.
Next, we measure the length of the waist.
pres02p nurses
After the measurement is done, we will make a simple arrangement for the board.
Arrange the back piece.
After the arrangement is done, we will seal it.
Since the board is symmetrical, we only need to do it once.
Select the free seam line.
As you can see, the seam line is very simple.
There is a blue point in the 2D seam line.
But now you can see that there is also a blue point in the 3D seam line.
After sewing, we will work on it.
Before the simulation, let's talk about the differences between these simulations.
This is not a new feature.
This needs to be emphasized.
Because in the process of doing technical support,
Everyone asked more about this.
You can see these four.
The first one is called GPU simulation.
GPU simulation is newly added in version 5.0 and 5.1.
If you download the new version,
This GPU simulation driver needs to be updated.
Although the GPU simulation is fast,
But relatively speaking, it is not very accurate to the simulation of the material.
Ordinary simulation is the one we use the most.
The next one is called completion simulation.
Completion simulation is used for sewing.
It can very accurately simulate the conflict between the fabric.
In this way, the material will not be penetrated during the sewing process.
Secret simulation can most accurately display the continuity of the fabric.
So when you make your own fabric,
After you finally improve the quality, you will have a secret simulation.
And when we switch to different simulations,
We can see that its simulation indicators are different.
We can see this secret simulation.
Its icon is red.
After simulation, it should be red.
It has a arrow at the bottom.
In completion simulation, it is red.
But there is no arrow.
Ordinary simulation is this ordinary blue.
GPU simulation is an empty simulation.
It is an arrow with an empty star.
Now we are using ordinary simulation.
Simulate this cloth.
After simulation, next.
After simulation, we will change the size of the virtual model.
Let's change the model a little bit higher.
Similarly, you can see that there is a height value in the menu.
And then it has a value.
You can see that the model is inflated.
Now there is a tool called the automatic numbering tool.
It can automatically number according to your model body shape.
It maintains the curve of the board.
That is, its curve does not change.
If there is a sticker on your board,
You can keep the sticker size.
When the board is numbering,
The sticker will not number.
If you don't number the board,
The sticker will also number.
Everyone knows that in cloud,
The lower the particle diameter, the slower the simulation.
It's the same when doing automatic numbering.
The lower your particle diameter,
The slower it numbers.
So I recommend everyone to change the particle diameter to 20.
It can number the fastest.
Click here to see its effect.
You can see that its numbering is now set.
In 2D, there is one.
There is a reference line in the previous version of the library.
Click here to see the reference line.
Now let's add a fabric for this cloth.
Click the Music Cartoon tab.
Click here to add the texture.
Let's separate the front pattern and choose a different pattern.
Normally, we usually have to hide the model in 3D to see the pattern on the back.
In the previous version, we couldn't see the pattern on the back of the costume on the second-party interface.
Now we can see the pattern on the back.
Let's change the color of the back.
We can see that there is a Palette Library.
This color is mainly used to add pantone colors.
In fact, there is a plus sign on the back of this 1.
But since the color of this plus sign is the same as the background color, we can't see it together.
Let's click here to see the pantone color library.
Because there are too many pantone colors, it divided the pantone colors into several colors.
Each color is divided into one.
We can choose the pantone color we need to import.
Let's change the color of the back.
Let's choose a pantone color.
In the 5.1 version, it only shows the normal map.
At this time, we choose the material in the preview.
We can add its normal map.
Let's save the material in the preview.
When saving the material, it will have a preview image.
You can use your added pattern.
You can also create your own image.
Here we choose the pattern.
Click to confirm.
Save it.
After saving the material,
Because I put it in the 5.1 version,
Let's take a look.
Here, it looks different.
You can see the preview of the material here.
This is convenient for us to check the picture later.
Next, let's change the pose of the virtual model.
Next, we are going to make the rotation set.
You can see the rotation set.
It is controlled by this button.
Click to confirm.
After that, it will not be Что.
Next, click to confirm.
It will not be What.
Click to confirm.
Next, we are going to update the 170.
There are some errors here.
Some details will appear when using the long version .
If you want to perform its details very well,
You need to lower the line setting of the version.
The lower the particle diameter of the board, the better its performance will be, but it has a disadvantage, which is that its simulation speed will be slower.
So for this part, we have added a new function called Selection.
We can reduce the number of particle diameters of the board.
We select the external line of the board and open Selection.
We can see that its particle diameter has become 1.
We switch to the web page to see and simulate.
We can see that its fold is formed, and we can change its height.
Next we add the foldable foldable axis on the side.
In the past, we could only add the line foldable axis and the foldable axis.
Now we can add the free foldable axis.
After adding the free foldable axis, we can see the effect of the foldable axis.
In addition to the foldable axis that is generated by itself, we can also choose the texture to represent its foldable axis.
We select this one.
We add a texture to it.
Then we change its width and color again.
In this way, the shape of the foldable axis on the side will change.
This function can be used to add different types of lines.
You can choose to add a texture.
Next, we add a sticker.
In the previous version, if you want to show a thick sticker, we recommend that you use the plate to increase its rendering thickness.
In the current version, we can use an illusion picture to show its thickness.
However, the effect of the illusion picture is that it cannot be seen in the 3D interface.
It must be seen in the rendering interface.
Let's open the rendering and take a look.
Since the illusion picture is a gray map, that is, the degree of bulge in the text is related to its grayness.
The whiter it is, the more obvious it is.
The darker it is, the less obvious it is.
We can see that its texture is not very smooth in the rendering interface.
This is mainly because we did not reduce its plate to 1.
Then let's talk about the properties of this illusion picture.
The first one is the degree.
The higher the degree, the more obvious the white bulge is.
Let's change it to 5.
We can see that the white bulge is more obvious.
Distance.
The more distance it is from the board, the farther it is.
That is, it is floating on the board.
The meaning of picking up is that it will not show any parts that are smaller than the value picked up above.
We input 2.
We can see that only white parts are displayed, and most of them are not displayed.
Maintain continuous is for OBJ files.
After opening continuous, it will delete a dividing line between OBJ components.
You know that in this case, it will be the drag function.
As you know, there are many different types of fabrics in CLO.
Every time we change the type of fabric,
we will pause and refresh the rendering interface.
Now, when we change the different fabric materials,
we can actually see the result of the rendering interface.
Let's switch to this one.
Then we switch to the other four types of materials.
We can also see the result of the rendering interface.
You can see that the difference between the current hair style and the previous hair style is that
the current hair style has added a preset hair attribute.
When we were doing hair styles in the past,
we were often asked what kind of hair style it was,
and how many parameters it should have.
For this question,
we added this preset hair attribute.
There are many different hair styles in this one,
including sea hair, angora yam hair, fox hair, water skin,
snake hair, dragon hair, rabbit hair, and so on.
We can switch to different hair styles to see its effect.
Now we switch to angora yam hair.
Then we switch to water skin.
When the current hair style has added a preset hair attribute,
you can see that the current hair style has added a preset hair attribute.
Let's switch back to the default hair style as well.
Here we can see that the current hair style has added a preset hair attribute,
and we have added the preset hair attribute here.
The new hair attribute for this set is called weight.
This way, it shows the direction of hair hair
in terms of the outside for the outside.
The bigger the pull force is,
the more smoothly it looks like in 4.3-mega-percent hair.
The x, y, z value means the larger the value, the more it is on the right side.
The x value of 10 is on the right side.
The y value of 10 is on the left side.
The z value of 10 is on the right side.
Next, let's take a look at the effects of different hairs.
This is Anglaise hair.
The next one is water-paint.
This is a woolen fabric.
The number of effects is large, so we will convert it to normal fabric.
Next, let's talk about other effects.
First, we convert it to the image video attribute.
Because 5.1 is the number of effects,
we added animation.
So in the image video attribute,
in addition to the image,
we also added an animation.
In other words, after you finish walking,
you can show the animation.
When saving the image,
we can choose whether to use the name of the project file
or use the user name.
Next, let's take a look at the lighting attribute.
In the lighting attribute,
the block to camera is mainly a light-locking lens.
In the previous version,
there was a blackout on the back side.
If we choose the block to camera,
this problem will disappear.
The next one is the display.
The display means that the HDR is displayed in the window.
In the previous version,
the intensity of lighting can be adjusted to 100.
Now it can be adjusted to 10,000.
Its exposure is very strong.
Next, let's take a look at the lens attribute.
We can zoom in and zoom out in the view.
Then there is a view direction,
spherical.
This is a three-dimensional direction.
The distance is its view.
Then the horizontal angle is rotated horizontally.
The vertical angle is rotated vertically.
There is an absolute between spherical and absolute.
This is the absolute direction.
It can only move in the horizontal direction of the water.
And the vertical direction of the water.
This is the distance between the two sides.
Next, let's take a look at the 5.1 of this dress.
It is a walk-through.
We can open this walk-through and take a look.
I mentioned earlier that in the rendering interface,
a new video attribute called animation has been added.
Let's take a look at the difference between rendering animation and a simple walk-through.
The first one is without a stage.
We can see that it is a
more high-definition walk-through.
The other one is a walk-through that adds a stage
and does not involve a model.
Now let's download another project file
to talk about some other functions.
This walk-through is made with a 3D walk-through tool.
You can see that it has some deformation at the end.
In the past, if the walk-through was deformed,
we would choose to do it with a version file.
Now we can edit the physical properties of the 3D walk-through.
We choose a more flat fabric for the 3D walk-through.
Then let's try some modeling.
Now you can see that it is not deformed and deformed.
In addition, we can see that there are two slides in this part.
If there is a hold-over in the slides,
You can choose the pattern by selecting the frame.
Next, let's take a look at the bottom of the zipper.
The bottom of the zipper is an OBJ link.
And this kind of clothing has a unique color mode.
The color is different under different modes.
Then we can see that this OBJ file has a pattern.
Then we select the file to export, export OBJ selected.
Then we put it in this folder.
We can see that when exporting this folder,
the first thing we can see here is called maintain single pattern coordinates.
Because this clothing has two colors,
we choose to maintain single pattern coordinates.
When it exports OBJ, it can export two patterns.
Then we can see that this clothing has two colors.
We export two OBJ files.
You save the absolute pattern in the file path.
Since this OBJ has a pattern,
if you delete the pattern in your original path,
then when you save it, its pattern will be lost.
If you don't delete it, its pattern will not be lost.
Let's take a look at this folder.
We can see that there are two OBJ files in it.
And there are three MTL files.
Just now,
when we export the OBJ,
there is another way to export the OBJ again.
The meaning of shared pattern coordinates is that
it only exports one OBJ file,
but it can export multiple MTL files.
Let's take a look.
You can see that it only has one OBJ file,
but it has multiple MTL files.
Next, let's talk about another function of the button.
If we want to increase the button on the front of this clothing,
but there is no button mark on this clothing,
now we can choose to create a button along the outline of the pattern.
We choose the outline of this pattern first,
and then select the button tool.
Press the right button on the outline.
We can see the button frame.
We can enter its value according to the need.
We can see that these three are already entered.
Here, I will teach you how to increase the button along the outline of the pattern.
Finally, we can see that in this 3D interface,
its hammer and hammer,
there is another display icon at the end.
Here, we can display the light controller,
display the wind controller,
and whether the model's shadow is displayed,
and whether the 3D grid is displayed.
That's all.
Today, I will show you the main new function of 5.1.
If you have any questions,
please go to our official website and search for the new function of 5.1.
If you want to know more details about 5.1,
There are relevant videos and text explanations in it.